Douglas Southall Freeman Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Correspondence, 1900-1954 (Box 4-120)
  - 1937-1939 (Box 28)
    - Carter, Louise, 1939-1941 See also same container, Carter, Howard
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Cheek, Leslie, 1938-1939
    - Chitwood, Dr. O. P., 1937-1939
    - Chorley, Kenneth, 1937-1939
    - Christian, T. J. J., 1939
    - Clayborne and Taylor, Inc., 1938
    - Cocke, Betty and Louise, 1937-1938
    - Coker, Mrs. David R., 1937-1939
    - Columbia University, 1937-1939
    - Cooke, Giles B., family, 1937-1938
    - Cooper, Myrtle, 1938
    - Coudert, Ferderic R., 1937-1938
    - Couper, William, 1938-1939
    - “Cr-Dn” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Darrow, Whitney, 1938-1939
    - Davis, Jackson, 1937-1939
    - DeWitt, John L., 1938-1939
    - Dictionary of American History, 1938
    - “Do-E” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (2 folders)
    - Early, Stephen, 1939
    - Eggleston, J. D., 1938-1939
    - Evans, John Gary, 1938-1939
    - “Fa-Fn” miscellaneous, 1937-1939 (Box 30)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1937-1939
    - Freeman, Allen W., 1937-1939
    - Freeman, Anne B., 1938-1939
    - Freeman, Douglas Southall, clippings, 1934-1938
    - Freeman, James Douglas, 1938-1939
    - Freeman, James E., 1937-1939
    - Freeman, Mary Tyler, 1937-1939, (2 folders)
    - “Fo-Gk” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (2 folders)
    - Gaines, Francis P., 1937-1938
    - Gillette, C. F., 1937-1939
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Glasgow, Ellen, 1937-1939
    - Goodloe, Henry L., 1938-1939
    - Godfrey, Colonel S. C., 1939
    - “Haa-Hd” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Harman, A. F., 1939
    - Hawkes, Herbert E. and Mrs., 1937-1939
    - “He-Ht” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (2 folders)
    - Hoffbauer, Charles, 1937-1939
    - Holmes, Mrs. George S., 1938-1939
    - Hotchkiss, Jedediah, papers, 1938
    - “Hu-Hz” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Hughes, Robert M., 1937-1938
    - Income tax, 1937-1939
    - Insurance, 1936-1939
    - “J-Ld” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (3 folders)
    - “Le-Ln” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (3 folders) (Box 32)
    - Lee, Robert E.
      - General, including copies of old documents, clippings, publications, and other source material, 1937-1939, (4 folders)
      - Errors, 1937-1939, (3 folders)
      - Lee's Lieutenants, 1937-1939, (3 folders)
    - Leitz, E., Inc., 1937
    - Lejeune, John A., 1937
    - Lewars, Elsie Singmaster, 1937-1938
    - Lewis, Edwin N., 1939
    - “Lo-Mb” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (2 folders)
    - Mann, Albert R., 1938-1939
    - Marshall, John, 1939
    - “Mc-Md” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - McCabe, E. R. W., 1937-1939
    - McCain, J. R., 1939
    - “Me-Mn” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Messersmith, George, 1938
    - Meyer, Wallace, 1938
    - “Mo-Mz” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Moffett, Mrs. George H., 1937-1938
    - Moreel, Ben, 1939
    - “N-Ph” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (3 folders) (Box 33)
    - Pemberton, John C., 1937-1939
    - Pender, William C., 1937-1939
    - Perkins, Maxwell E., 1937-1939
    - Phillips, Charles H., 1937-1939 See also Container 13, same heading, (2 folders)
    - “Pi-Pz” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Price, James H., 1937-1939
    - “Q” miscellaneous, 1938-1939
    - “Ra-Rz” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (2 folders)
    - Rockefeller, John D. and John D., Jr., 1937-1939
    - Rockefeller memorial, 1937-1938
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1938-1939
    - Ruddock, Albert B., 1939
    - Russell, R. E. L., 1939
    - “Sa-Sd” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (2 folders)
    - Scribner, Charles, 1938-1939
    - Scribner's Magazine, 1939
    - “Se-Sj” miscellaneous, 1927-1939
    - Sites, Maud, 1937-1939
    - “Sk-Ss” miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 34)
    - Smith, Chard Powers, 1938-1939
    - Spaulding, O. L., 1937-1938
    - Spofford, Florence P., 1938
    - “St-Sz” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Sterne, M. H., 1936-1939
    - Sully, Julia, 1937-1939
    - Suter, Thomas L., 1937-1939
    - “T” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Tax receipts, 1936-1939
    - Taylor, Charles H., 1937-1938
    - Thomason, John W., 1937-1938
    - Tomorrow Club, 1938
    - “U-V” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Von Boetticher, General Friedrich, 1937-1939
    - “Wa-Wh” miscellaneous, 1937-1939, (2 folders)
    - Weddell, Alexander W., 1937-1939
    - Westbourne (house), 1938-1939
    - “Wi-Wz” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
    - Wickham, Henry T., 1938
    - Will, 1935-1936
    - Williams (general), 1937-1939
    - Williams, Mrs. A. D., 1938
    - Wines, 1937-1938
    - Wood, J. E., 1939
    - “X-Z” miscellaneous, 1937-1939
  - 1940-1941 (Box 35)
    - “A” miscellaneous, 19410-1941
    - Ackerman, Carl W., 1940-1941
    - Alden, Carrol S., 1940
    - Allen, Clyde P., 1940-1941
    - Amory, C. P. Inc., 1932, 1941
    - Anchor Post Fence, 1941
    - Ashworth, Osbourne O., 1940-1941
    - “Ba-Bh” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Barbed-Wire Horizons, 1940
    - “Bi-Bq” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Boatwright, Frederick William, 1940-1941
    - “Br-Bt” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Brown, William Adams, 1940
    - Brucker, Herbert, 1940-1941
    - Bryan, David Tennant, 1939-1940
    - Bryan, John Stewart, 1940-1941
    - Burke, Mrs. Moncure, 1941
    - “Bu-Bz” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1940-1941
    - Byrd, Harry Flood, 1940
    - “Ca-Cg” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Carnegie Endowment, 1940
    - Carrol, Eleanor, 1941
    - Carter, Louise, 1940
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Cheek, Leslie and Mary Tyler, 1940-1941
    - “Co-Cq” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Columbia University, 1940-1941
    - Cook, Roy Bird, 1940
    - “Cr-Cz” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - “Da-Dn” miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 36)
    - Dabney, Virginius, 1940
    - Darden, Golgate W., Jr., 1941-1942
    - Darrow, Whitney, 1940-1941
    - Davis, Jackson, 1940-1941
    - “Do-Fz” miscellaneous, 1940-1941, (4 folders)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - Frank, Glenn, 1940
    - Freeman, Allen W., 1940-1941
    - Freeman, Anne B., 1940-1941
    - Freeman, Douglas Southall, news clippings, photographs, notes, etc., 1940
    - Freeman, James Douglas, 1940-1941
    - Freeman, James E., 1940-1941
    - “Ga-Gk” miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 37)
    - General Education Board, 1940
    - Gillette, Charles F., 1940-1941
    - Gilliam, Charles Edgar, 1939-1940
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Glasgow, Ellen, 1940
    - Godfrey, S. C., 1940-1941
    - Graham, Frank and Mrs., 1940
    - Grant, General W. S., 1941
    - “Haa-Hal” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Hall, Wilmer L., 1940
    - “Ham-Hd” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Hawkes, Herbert E. and Mrs., 1940-1941
    - “He-Ht” miscellaneous, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - Hoffbauer, Charles, 1939-1941
    - Holmes, George S., 1940-1941
    - Holloway, Anne, 1941
    - “Hu-I” miscellaneous, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - Income tax, 1939-1942, (2 folders)
    - Insurance, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - “J” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Johnston, J. Ambler, 1940
    - “Ka-Kk” miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 38)
    - Kane, Keith, 1940
    - Kilbourne, C. E., 1940-1941
    - King, E. P., Jr., 1940
    - “Kl-Ln” miscellaneous, 1940-1941, (3 folders)
    - Lee, Robert E.
      - General, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
      - Errors, 1940-1941
      - Birthday address, 1941
      - Lee's Lieutenants
    - Lewis, W. M., 1940
    - “Lo-Mb” miscellaneous, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - Marshall, George C., 1940
    - “Mc-Md” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - McCabe, E. R. W., 1940-1941
    - McCain, J. R., 1940
    - “Me-Mn” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Meyer, Eugene, 1940-1941
    - “Mo-N” miscellaneous, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - News Leader, 1940
    - “O” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - “Pa-Ph” miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 39)
    - Pemberton, John C., 1940-1941
    - Percival, Alan V., 1940-1941
    - Perkins, Maxwell E., 1940-1941
    - Phi Beta Kappa associates, 1940-1941
    - “Pi-Pz” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Poindexter, Eldridge W., 1940
    - Powell, Noble C., 1940
    - Price, James H., 1940-1941
    - “Ra-Rn” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Richmond, University of, 1941
    - Rehkopf, Ned B., 1940
    - “Ro-Rz” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Robertson, Willis, 1940-1941
    - Rockefeller, John D. and John D., III, 1940-1941
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1940-1941
    - Rockefeller memorial, 1938-1941
    - Ruddock, Albert B., 1941
    - “Sa-Sb” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Satterfield, Dave E., 1941
    - “Sc-Sd” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Scribner, Charles, 1941
    - “Se-Ss” miscellaneous, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - Smith (general), 1940-1941
    - “St-Sz” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Sully, J., 1940-1941
    - State Defense Council (Virginia), 1940
    - “T” miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 40)
    - Tapp property, 1940
    - Tax receipts, 1940-1941
    - “U-V” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Van Kuyck, Hugo, 1941
    - Warren, Robert B., 1940-1941
    - “Wa-Wh” miscellaneous, 1940-1941, (2 folders)
    - Weddel, Alexander W., 1940-1941
    - White, Mrs. Walter C., 1940-1941
    - “Wi-Wz” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
    - Wilkins, Raymond S., 1939-1940
    - Willits, Joseph H., 1939-1941
    - Williams (general), 1940-1941
    - Williams, Murat, 1940-1941
    - Wood, J. E., 1940-1941
    - Woodrum, Clifton W., 1941
    - “X-Z” miscellaneous, 1940-1941
  - 1942 (Box 41)
    - “A” miscellaneous
    - Ackerman, Carl W.
    - ABC Board
    - Allen (general)
    - Ambler, Gordon B.
    - Anderson (general)
    - Apperly, Frank L.
    - Ashworth, Osbourne O.
    - “Ba-Bq” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Binford, Jesse H.
    - Boatwright, Frederick William
    - Books
    - “Br-Bt” miscellaneous
    - Brucker, Herbert
    - Bryan, John Stewart
    - “Bu-Bz” miscellaneous
    - Bullitt, W. M.
    - Byrd, Harry Flood
    - “Ca-Cg” miscellaneous
    - Carmichael, Chancellor O. C.
    - Carnegie Endowment
    - Carter, Louise
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous (Box 42)
    - Cheek, Leslie, Jr., and Mary Tyler
    - “Co-Cq” miscellaneous
    - Coleman, R. V.
    - Conrad, Bryan
    - “Cr-Dn” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Darden, Colgate W., Jr.
    - Darrow, Whitney
    - DeVoy, S. Elizabeth
    - “Do-Dz” miscellaneous, 1941-1942
    - Dodson, Griffith
    - “E” miscellaneous
    - Eckenrode, H. J.
    - Egger, Rowland
    - “Fa-Fz” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B.
    - Freeman, Allen W.
    - Freeman, Anne B.
    - Freeman, James Douglas
    - “Ga-Gk” miscellaneous
    - Gaines, Francis P.
    - Gillette, Charles F.
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous
    - Godfrey, S. C.
    - Greene, Joseph I.
    - Guerry, Alexander
    - “Haa-Hd” miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Hawkes, Herbert E. and Mrs.
    - “He-Ht” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Holloway, Anne M.
    - Hopkins, Garland Evans
    - “Hu-I” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Insurance
    - Income tax
    - “J” miscellaneous
    - Jones (general)
    - “Ka-Kk” miscellaneous
    - Kilbourne, C. E.
    - “Kl-Ln” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Lee, Robert E., Lee's Lieutenants, 1941-1942
    - Lewars, Mrs. E. S.
    - Lewis, Tracy
    - “Lo-Lz” miscellaneous
    - “Ma-Mb” miscellaneous (Box 44)
    - Macleish, Archibald
    - Mann, Albert R.
    - Marshall, George C.
    - Marks, Arnold
    - Marsteller, Emlyn H.
    - “Mc-Md” miscellaneous
    - McCarthy, Frank
    - “Me-Mn” miscellaneous
    - Meyer, Eugene
    - Meyer, Wallace
    - “Mz-Ph” miscellaneous, (4 folders)
    - Patterson, Robert P.
    - Pemberton, John C.
    - Percival, Margaret
    - Perkins, Maxwell E.
    - “Pi-Pz” miscellaneous
    - Poindexter, E. W.
    - Pomeroy, Hugh R.
    - Porter, Charles W.
    - “Q-Rn” miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - Receipts
    - Richardson, Eudora Ramsey
    - “Ro-Rz” miscellaneous, 1941-1942
    - Robertson, A. Willis
    - Rockefeller Foundation
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr.
    - Ruddock, Merritt
    - Russell, R. E. L.
    - “Sa-Sd” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Scribner, Charles
    - “Se-Ss” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Smith (general)
    - Southern Historical Society, 1941-1942, (2 folders)
    - “St-Sz” miscellaneous
    - State Defense Council (Virginia), 1941-1942, (2 folders)
    - “T” miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Tax receipts
    - Taylor (general)
    - Thalhimer, William B.
    - Town hall
    - “U-Wh” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Weber, William C.
    - Weddell, Alexander W. and Mrs.
    - Wheeler, Mrs. Harry
    - White, Mrs. Walter C.
    - “Wi-Wz” miscellaneous, 1941-1942
    - Wise, Charlotte J.
    - “X-Z” miscellaneous
  - 1943 (Box 47)
    - “A” miscellaneous
    - Ackerman, Carl W.
    - Anderson (general)
    - Armour, Alexander W.
    - Ashworth, Osbourne O.
    - Automobiles
    - “Ba-Bh” miscellaneous
    - Barton, Robert T.
    - “Bi-Bq” miscellaneous
    - Billikopf, Jacob
    - Bishop, P. P.
    - Blackford, Randolph F.
    - Bobbitt, H. I.
    - Boatwright, Frederick William
    - Books
    - Boushall, Thomas C.
    - Boyd, Julian P.
    - “Br-Bt” miscellaneous
    - British embassy
    - Brown (general)
    - Brucker, Herbert
    - Bryan, John Stewart
    - Bryan, Tennant
    - “Bu-Bz” miscellaneous
    - Byrd, Harry Flood
    - “Ca-Cg” miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Campbell, T. M.
    - Carnegie Endowment
    - Carrol, Eleanor
    - Catharpin
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous
    - Cheek, Leslie and Mary Tyler
    - Christian, Andrew D.
    - Clemen, Rudolf A.
    - “Co-Cq” miscellaneous
    - Codd, L. A.
    - Coleman, R. V.
    - Colie, Runion
    - Conrand, Bryan
    - Core, Mrs. Carl
    - “Cr-Cz” miscellaneous
    - Cuyler, T. Cruger
    - “Da-Dn” miscellaneous
    - Darrow, Whitney
    - Davis, Jackson
    - Diggs, Gaius W.
    - “Do-Dz” miscellaneous
    - Dodds, Harold
    - “E” miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - Eckenrode, H. J.
    - Edmonds, James E.
    - Egger, Rowland
    - Eggleston, J. D.
    - “Fa-Fn” miscellaneous
    - Farnum, George R.
    - First and Merchants Bank
    - “Fo-Fz” miscellaneous
    - Fosdick, Raymond D.
    - Freeman, Allen W.
    - Freeman, Anne B.
    - Freeman, James Douglas
    - “Ga-Gk” miscellaneous
    - Gaines, Francis P.
    - Garnett, W. E.
    - Geddes, Donald Porter (editor)
    - Gillette, Charles E.
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous
    - Godbey, Allen Howard
    - Goddard, Calvin
    - Godfrey, S. C.
    - Goodloe, Henry L.
    - Greene, Joseph I.
    - Greenfield, Kent Roberts
    - Greer, Allen J.
    - “Haa-Hd” miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Harris, H. Hiter
    - Hawkes, Harry E. and Mrs.
    - “He-Ht” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Hoffbauer, Charles
    - “Hu-Hz” miscellaneous
    - Hughes, Emma
    - Hummel, Edward A.
    - “I” miscellaneous
    - Income tax
    - Insurance
    - “J” miscellaneous
    - Jenkins, Willard W.
    - Jones (general)
    - “Ka-Kk” miscellaneous
    - Kane, R. Keith and Mrs.
    - “Kl-Kz” miscellaneous
    - Krout, John A.
    - “La-Ld” miscellaneous
    - Lanier, Mrs. Charles D.
    - Lawyers Title Insurance Co., 1941
    - “Le-Ln” miscellaneous
    - Lee, Robert E.
      - Lee's Lieutenants, 1941-1943, (2 folders)
      - Errors
    - Lewars, Mrs. E. S.
    - Lewis, Charles Lee
    - Lisle, Clifton
    - “Lo-Lz” miscellaneous
    - Lowe, S. F.
    - “Ma-Mb” miscellaneous (Box 51)
    - Macleish, Archibald
    - Marshall, George C.
    - “Mc-Md” miscellaneous
    - McCarthy, Frank
    - “Me-Mn” miscellaneous
    - Meyer, Wallace
    - “Mo-N” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Neblett, William H.
    - Nevins, Allan
    - Newcomen Society
    - Northwestern University
    - “O-Ph” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Parkinson, Thomas I.
    - Patterson, Robert P.
    - Percival, Margaret
    - Perkins, Maxwell E.
    - “Pi-Rn” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
    - Richards, Gertrude R. B.
    - Richey, Thomas B. and Mrs.
    - Rixey, Lilian
    - “Ro-Rz” miscellaneous
    - Robertson, A. Willis
    - Russel, Robert E. L.
    - “Sa-Sb” miscellaneous (Box 52)
    - Satterfield, Dave E.
    - “Sc-Sd” miscellaneous
    - Schenck, Paul W.
    - Scribner, Charles
    - “Se-Sj” miscellaneous
    - Sexton, W. T.
    - Shotwell, James T.
    - “Sk-Ss” miscellaneous
    - Snyder, Franklin B.
    - Southern Historical Society papers
    - “St-Sz” miscellaneous
    - Steel, Mrs. Albert and family
    - Stevens, David H.
    - “T” miscellaneous
    - Tax receipts
    - Taylor, Henry
    - Trigg, Emma Grey
    - Trimble, Ridgeway
    - “U-Wd” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Wahrman, Ben
    - Wall, Jane D.
    - Wanliss, Marion
    - Ware, J. G.
    - Weddell, Alexander W. and Mrs.
    - “We-Wh” miscellaneous
    - White, Mrs. Walter C.
    - “Wi-Wz” miscellaneous
    - Wicker, John J.
    - Widmer, William
    - Wiley, B. I.
    - Wilkins, Raymond S.
    - Williams (general)
    - Wilmer, W. H.
    - Wilshin, Francis F.
    - Wilson (general)
    - Wise, Charlotte J.
    - Wood, J. E.
    - Wright, A. R.
    - Writers' War Board
    - Wysor, W. G.
    - “X-Z” miscellaneous
    - Zimmerman, J. McC.
  - 1944 (Box 53)
    - “A” miscellaneous
    - ABC board
    - Ackerman, Carl W.
    - American Society of Historians, 1943-1944
    - Ashworth, Osbourne O.
    - “Ba-Bh” miscellaneous
    - Barr, Earl W.
    - “Bi-Bq” miscellaneous
    - Billikopf, Jacob
    - Board, C. F.
    - Boatwright, Frederick William
    - Books
    - Boyd, Julian P.
    - “Br-Bt” miscellaneous
    - Brown (general)
    - Brown, John Stewart
    - Byan, Tennant
    - Brucker, Herbert
    - “Bu-Bz” miscellaneous
    - Buck, J. L. Blair
    - Burge, Martin H.
    - Burke, Pauline W.
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray
    - Byrd, Harry Flood
    - “Ca-Cg” miscellaneous (Box 54)
    - Campbell-Ewald Co.
    - Carnegie Endowment
    - Carroll, Eleanor
    - Carter, Robert H.
    - Carter, Spencer L.
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous
    - Chappell, Mrs. F. V.
    - Cheek, Leslie and Mary Tyler
    - Christian, Andrew D.
    - Clemen, Rudolf A.
    - “Co-Cq” miscellaneous
    - Coleman, J. Walter, 1943-1944
    - Coleman, R. V.
    - Colie, Runion
    - Commager, Henry Steele
    - Corson, Fred Pierce
    - Council, Carroll B.
    - “Cr-Cz” miscellaneous
    - Crouch, Kenneth E.
    - Cuyler, T. Kruger
    - “Da-Dn” miscellaneous
    - Darden, Colgate W., Jr.
    - Darrow, Whitney
    - Davis, Jackson
    - Devoy, S. Elizabeth
    - “Do-Dz” miscellaneous
    - Dodds, Harold
    - Dodson, E. Griffith
    - Dominion Securities Corp.
    - “E-Fz” miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - Forrestal, James Vincent
    - Fosdick, Raymond B.
    - Freeman, Allen W.
    - Freeman, Anne B.
    - Freeman, Hamner G., 1936-1944
    - Freeman, James Douglas
    - “Ga-Gk” miscellaneous
    - Gaines, Frank P., 1943
    - Garrett, Mrs. Johnson
    - General Education Board, 1943-1944
    - Gernhardt, C. H.
    - “Gl-Gz” miscellaneous
    - Glasgow, Ellen
    - Goddard, Galvin
    - Godfrey, S. C.
    - Gravins, William F.
    - Green, James A.
    - Greene, Joseph I.
    - Greenfield, Kent Roberts
    - Greer, Allen
    - Grolier Society
    - “Haa-Hal” miscellaneous
    - Hall, Wilmer L.
    - “Ham-Hd” miscellaneous (Box 56)
    - Hamlin, Percy G.
    - Harris. H. Hiter
    - Harris, William A., Sr. and Jr.
    - “He-Hn” miscellaneous, 1943-1944
    - “Ho-Ht” miscellaneous
    - Hoes, Laurence G.
    - Hoffbauer, Charles
    - Holloway, Anne M.
    - “Hu-I” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Income tax
    - Insurance
    - “J” miscellaneous
    - Johnston, Joseph E.
    - “Ka-Kk” miscellaneous
    - Kane, Keith and Mrs.
    - Kendig, Perry F.
    - King, Ernest J.
    - “Kl-Kz” miscellaneous
    - Krout, John A.
    - “La-Ld” miscellaneous
    - Labaree, Leonard W.
    - “Le-Ln” miscellaneous
    - Lee, Robert E.
      - General, 1943-1944
      - Lee's Lieutenants
        - Maps
        - Pictures
        - Manuscript records
    - Lewars, Mrs. E. S.
    - “Lo-Lz” miscellaneous (Box 57)
    - Lord, Edward T. S.
    - Lovenstein, Meno
    - Lynde, S. A.
    - “Ma-Mb” miscellaneous
    - Mcbride, Van Dyk
    - Malone, Dumas
    - Mann, A. R.
    - Marshall, George C.
    - Martin, George R.
    - “Mc-Md” miscellaneous
    - McCain, J. R.
    - McCarthy, Frank
    - McAuliffe, M. J.
    - McCloy, J. J.
    - “Me-Mn” miscellaneous
    - Meade, Robert D., 1943
    - Meyer, Eugene and Agnes
    - Meyer, Wallace
    - “Mo-Mz” miscellaneous
    - Moses, Lionel B.
    - “N” miscellaneous
    - Nimitz, C. W.
    - Nevins, Allan
    - Norris, Ernest
    - Northington, O. F.
    - “O-Ph” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Patterson, R. P.
    - Percival, Mrs. Alan
    - Perkins, Maxwell E.
    - “Pi-Pz” miscellaneous
    - Pomfret, John E.
    - “Q” miscellaneous
    - “Ra-Rn” miscellaneous (Box 58)
    - Richey, Thomas B. and Mrs.
    - Richmond, University of
    - “Ro-Rz” miscellaneous
    - Robertson, A. Willis
    - Rockefeller Foundation
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
    - Ruddock, A. B.
    - “Sa-Sd” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Scribner, Charles
    - “Se-Ss” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Smith (general), 1942-1944
    - Southern Railway
    - “St-Sz” miscellaneous
    - Steuart, Richard D.
    - Stevens, David
    - Stewart, Miss A. C.
    - Sully, Julia
    - “T” miscellaneous
    - Tax receipts
    - Trimble, I.. Ridgeway
    - Truman, Harry S.
    - “U-V” miscellaneous
    - Van Doren, Carl
    - Van Doren, Mark
    - “Wa-Wh” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Weaver, Warren
    - Weber, William C.
    - Weddell, Alexander W. and Mrs.
    - Wellford, B. Rand
    - “Wi-Wz” miscellaneous
    - Will
    - Williams (general)
    - Williams, Ben Ames
    - Willits, Joseph H.
    - Wise, John Dana, 1941
    - “X-Z” miscellaneous
  - 1945 (Box 59)
    - “A” miscellaneous, 1945
    - ABC board, 1945
    - Ackerman, Carl W., 1945
    - Adams, Theodore F, 1945
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1945
    - Anderson (general), 1945
    - Armour, Alexander W., 1945
    - Ashworth, Osbourne O.
    - “Ba-Bh” miscellaneous
    - Bailey, John Wendell
    - Barton, Robert T.
    - Beasley, Norman
    - Benjamin, Roy
    - “Bi-Bq” miscellaneous
    - Billikopf, Jacob
    - Bisset, Walter D., 1944-1945
    - Blackford memoirs
    - Board, C. F.
    - Boatwright, Frederick William
    - Books, 1944-1945
    - Boushall, Thomas C.
    - Bowers, Gamble III
    - Boyd, Julian P.
    - “Br-Bt” miscellaneous
    - Bright, J. F.
    - Brown (general)
    - Bruce, A. D.
    - Brucker, Herbert
    - Bryan, John Stewart
    - Bryan, Tennant
    - Bryant, Joseph M.
    - “Bu-Bz” miscellaneous
    - Buck, J. L. Blair
    - Burke, Pauline W.
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray
    - Byrd, Harry Flood
    - “Ca-Cg” miscellaneous (Box 60)
    - Cameron, Donald F.
    - Campbell-Ewald Co.
    - Carnegie Endowment
    - Caroll, Eleanor
    - Carter, Spencer L.
    - Cary, John B.
    - Caudle, Mrs. Theron Lamar
    - “Ch-Cn” miscellaneous
    - Chase, Francis S.
    - Chase, Harry W.
    - Cheek, James H.
    - Cheek, Leslie and Mary Tyler
    - Christian, Andrew D.
    - Citizens' Association
    - “Co-Cq” miscellaneous
    - Columbia University
    - Commager, Henry Steele
    - Compton, Karl T.
    - Confederate Museum
    - “Cr-Cz” miscellaneous
    - Crouch, Kenneth E.
    - Cuyler, T. Cruger
    - “Da-Dn” miscellaneous
    - Darden, Colgate W.
    - Darrow, Whitney
    - Davis, Jackson
    - Dayton, Fred E.
    - Denison, S. L.
    - DeVoy, Elizabeth
    - Diggs, Gaius W.
    - “Do-Dz” miscellaneous
    - Dodds, Harold
    - Durkin, Joseph
    - “E” miscellaneous (Box 61)
    - Edwards, Horace H.
    - “Fa-Fn” miscellaneous
    - Falls, Oswald B., 1939-1945
    - “Fo-Fz” miscellaneous
    - Forrestal, James V.
    - Fosdick, Raymond B.
    - Freeman, Allen W.
    - Freeman, Anne B.
    - Freeman, Douglas Southall, (2 folders)
    - Freeman, Hamner G.
    - Freeman, James Douglas
    - “Ga-Gk” miscellaneous
    - Gaines, Francis P.